[Now Chatting
============](https://www.hinow.tv/)

HiNow Privacy Policy
====================

Scope of this Privacy Policy
----------------------------

This privacy policy is applicable to how the HiNow handles personally identifiable information that is left when users log in to the website and server, as well as other personally identifiable information shared with our business partners. This privacy policy is not applicable to organizations that do not belong to the HiNow or non- HiNow employees. This privacy policy constitutes an inseparable part of the HiNow User Agreement and must be read together with the HiNow User Agreement including but not limited to Clause 6 (on Privacy Protection) of the HiNow User Agreement.

Collection and Use of Information
---------------------------------

The HiNow will collect your personally identifiable information when you register a HiNow account, use other HiNow products or services, access HiNow webpages, or participate in promotional or prize winning games. The HiNow also collects personally identifiable information from our business partners. When you register a HiNow account, we will ask for your name, email address, interests, birthday, gender and personal webpage, in addition to a personal profile. Once you are successfully registered with the HiNow, we will be able to identify you when you log in to the server. The HiNow automatically receives and records the information on your browser and server logs, including your IP address, information in the HiNow cookies and your browsing history. The HiNow uses this information to enhance the quality of the video services that we provide and to improve the effectiveness to better tailor our services to your interests and needs.

Data Deletion
-------------

You can delete your account at any time in the Hinow settings by clicking on ‘Delete Account’. If you ask us to delete your account, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to remove your data from our servers, subject to any applicable legal or other requirements to maintain certain records of your personally identifiable data. Please note: when you delete your account, you will no longer be able to use our services, and your profile will no longer be accessible or visible to other users.

Disclosure and Sharing of Information
-------------------------------------

When you submit the information, it shall be deemed as your consent to the HiNow’s regarding the collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information by the HiNow. The HiNow will never display, rent or sell your personally identifiable information to others. The following circumstances are excluded: When your desired products and services can only be provided if your personal information is disclosed; When we are required to provide information to the companies that provide products or services on our behalf; (unless we notify you otherwise, these companies do not have the right to use your personally identifiable information); When we are required to comply with a court summons, court order or to comply with a legal process; When we discover that you have violated the terms of use of the HiNow, HiNow global village or any other products or services. The HiNow is not responsible for any collection, disclosure and/or use of your personal information provided by you to any third party's website which may be linked to or from our website.

Cookies
-------

The HiNow will set or access HiNow cookies on your computer. The HiNow allows those companies that publish advertisements on our webpages to set or access cookies on user computers. Other companies will use cookies in accordance with their own privacy policies, and cannot access cookies used by the HiNow. In performing operations associated with our products and services, the HiNow uses web beacons to retrieve cookies from our website.

Web Beacons (if applicable)
---------------------------

Our webpages include electronic images (known as a "pixel GIF" or a "beacon") that allow the website to calculate the number of webpage users or users that have saved a certain cookie. The ways in which the HiNow uses beacons include:

Beacons used within the HiNow
-----------------------------

The HiNow uses beacons on the website to calculate the total number of users and to identify registered users using saved HiNow cookies. We are able to provide customized webpage services when you are on non-hinow.tv websites by saving HiNow cookies.

Web beacons are used outside of the HiNow domain
------------------------------------------------

The HiNow uses website beacons to collect data for partner websites; relevant data is also used for statistical purposes. The HiNow user data recorded by website beacons are compiled and made available to our partners as aggregate data for reference purposes. Aggregate data includes information such as user count and usage, but does not include any personally identifiable data. When the HiNow places website beacons to collect data for our partners, we require our partners to inform users on their privacy policy page that the webpage uses website beacons. N.B. This option will only be recorded in your current browser and will not be recorded in your user history. Therefore, to completely block the beacon, you must click on the above link on all of your computers and browsers.

HTML Emails
-----------

The HiNow typically adds a beacon when sending emails in HTML format (emails containing images) to count the number of opened messages. Typically, electronic images are considered to be part of the webpage and, including banner ads, can all be used as beacons. Therefore, beacons can be added to all advertisements placed by the HiNow. The HiNow tracks certain usage behavior. Information collected from web beacons are used to understand how customers use our products, provide more accurate reports and enhance the effectiveness of our marketing.

Editing Personal Account Information and Preferences
----------------------------------------------------

At any time, you have the right to edit your HiNow account information and preferences, including whether you would like to receive information on the latest products from the HiNow.

Security Safeguards
-------------------

Your HiNow account is password protected to ensure the security of your privacy and information. Under certain conditions, the HiNow uses the universally accepted SSL encryption system to ensure the security of information transfer.

Amendments to the Privacy Policy
--------------------------------

The HiNow periodically makes changes to the privacy policy. If there are significant changes to the privacy policy, we will promptly notify users by posting the relevant terms in a prominent position on the webpage.

HiNow Community Convention
==========================

HiNow is devoted to providing global users with a real-time platform for them to find and create diversified novel interactive contents through online live video. To maintain healthy and safe live video on HiNow platform, a series of community conventions are established, aimed to ensure good user experience. We commit to keep healthy and safe HiNow in all aspects; however, no 100% assurance exists given a lot of objective conditions. Any user’s breaches of following terms and rules may lead to suspension of our services and even permanent ban.

It should also be noted that, if applicable, we’ll have the right to tell on any suspected criminal act to local public security organ.

1\. No Violence and/or Self-mutilation
--------------------------------------

Security is of top priority with HiNow. We frown on any act involving in forced threat and self-mutilation. If we’re aware of any risk of destruction or immediate threat against public security, we’ll delete such offensive contents and report them to enforcement agency. Also, threat against other is absolutely intolerant, or else the offender will be permanently banned from HiNow services.

2\. No Nudity or Broad Words & Acts
-----------------------------------

Any user in front of the lens must keep attired. Any user making live video in bad dressing will be suspended or permanently banned from HiNow services. Live user is prohibited showing up flesh that should be hidden by dress. HiNow prohibits seducing nudity in the name of any person, any offender upon discovery will be provisionally or permanently banned from HiNow services. Female live user must keep bosom moderately dressed, or else she will be provisionally or permanently banned from HiNow services

The user is prohibited from:

Vulgar, offensive or broad words before the lens or in live chat;

Showing his/her or other’s offensive or pornographic picture;

Sex or sexual behavior, or showing sex doll or sexual dance;

3\. No Comments of Fraud, Harassment or Hatred
----------------------------------------------

The user must respect other members of the community. It’s intolerant for HiNow of ridicule, fraud, racism or harassment against other users in the community. We do regard free speech, but we do not permit personal abuse based on race, nationality, religion, sex, gender, sexual orientation, disability or other illness.

4\. No Use of Prohibited Goods
------------------------------

Live use of prohibited goods, doping items or smoking or drinking is forbidden.

5\. No Use by Minor
-------------------

HiNow is designed for the group of users more than 18 years old, minors under this age are banned from live access, and we’ll close live video services to minor users. Cover girl/boy is not allowed. Minor live object is not allowed.

6\. No Publication of Personal Contact Information
--------------------------------------------------

Unauthorized publication of other’s personal information is forbidden, including but not limited to email address, telephone number or residence. Also, you’re seriously reminded of protecting your personal information and preventing them from unintentional disclosure.

7\. No Deceiving Emergency Organ or Hotline with False Information
------------------------------------------------------------------

It’s absolutely intolerant for HiNow of the user deceiving emergency organ or hotline with false information, and any user in connection with the said behavior will be permanently banned from HiNow services.

8\. No Inducing or Instigating Noncompliance
--------------------------------------------

Any inducement of sexual behavior or illegal behavior of community member is forbidden. Also, any guiding or manipulating other members for producing pornographic picture or soliciting personal information is forbidden.

Moreover, we forbid illegal business activity, including but not limited to multilevel marketing.

We forbid instigation of noncompliance, regardless during chat or live broadcast.

9\. No Spam Transmission
------------------------

Any action preventing normal and orderly chat of other users by repeated entry or in other way is forbidden. Likewise, publicity of pornographic, obscene or malicious website link is forbidden. HiNow reserves the right to dispose of any account involving in the above behavior.

10.Legal Jurisdiction
---------------------

This Agreement shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Hong Kong, without regard to choice of law principles. Any dispute arising out of or in connection with this Agreement, including any question regarding its existence, validity or termination, shall be referred to and finally resolved by arbitration administered by the Hong Kong International Arbitration Centre in accordance with the Arbitration Rules of the Hong Kong International Arbitration Centre for the time being in force, which rules are deemed to be incorporated by reference in this clause. The seat of the arbitration shall be Hong Kong. The language of the arbitration shall be Chinese.

Address: RM4, 16/F, HO KING COMM CTR, 2-16 FAYUEN ST, MONGKOK KOWLOON, HONG KONG.

This site/app is oppreated by Hinow Limited.

* [Twitter](https://twitter.com/HiNowApp)·

* © 2017 Hinow (HongKong) Limited·
* [Support](mailto:service@hinow.tv)·
* [Contact](mailto:censor.kao@hinow.tv)·
* [Privacy Policy](https://www.hinow.tv/tos-link.html)·
